WE ARE A TEAM
Whether you plant or water, we are a team.
Each will be rewarded for what he or she does because we are all Christ's co-worker.
WE ARE A TEAM
We are given different spiritual gifts; that is why our ministrations are different.
Because we have different spiritual what?
Gifts.
That is why our what?.. Are different.
We are all Christ's co-workers but one thing is sure - the foundation has already been laid.
For no one can lay the foundation because the foundation has already been laid.
The foundation is Jesus Christ and I will build on the foundation of Jesus Christ.
WE ARE A TEAM
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God`s power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophesies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from the Synagogue, Church of all Nations.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations And Changing The World
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 13/07/2018